Alexander, Gabriel Additional Arbitration Files 5678
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files
1956-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alexander, Gabriel
5678
19 cubic feet
19 linear ft.
Case files.
Collective labor agreements
3121934
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 10, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5133: Gabriel Alexander Arbitration Files 5602: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5789: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Alexander, Gabriel
3121934
- Cleveland Cliffs Iron Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4950, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  La Fountaine - Harris Grievance - Work Assignments - Overtime. Closed November 4, 1975.
- Dayton Power and Light Company and United Workers of America, Grievance Number 821, Local Number 175, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Promotions; Physical Disability; Medical Standards. Closed January 10, 1973.
- Dayton Power and Light Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 175, Grievance Number 75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Grievance Procedure: Arbitrability. Closed November 15, 1976.
- The Detroit Edison Company and UWUA, Local 223, Case Number 54 30 0959 74, Grievance Number UG-651-P, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Fred D. Bowman. Closed April 2, 1976.
- The Detroit Edison Company and the Utility Workers Union of America, Local 223, Case 54 30 0647 75 Grievances MD-524, MD-525., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Refusal to perform work assignments. Closed October 19, 1976.
- Gardner-Denver Company and International Association of Machinists, Local 1503, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Classification Grievance. Closed January 17, 1975.
- General Foods Corporation and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 337, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Health and Safety: Periodic Physical Examinations. Grievance dated August 15, 1972. Closed January 10, 1973.
- Grand Haven Public Schools and Service Employees International Union, Local 586, Grievance Number A I-1., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Classification: General Help/Baker-Cook. Closed January 10, 1975
- Granite City Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 68, Grievance Number 66-72-2., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Scheduling. Closed May 15, 1973.
- Granite City Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 68, Grievance Number 92-72-3., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Equalization of Overtime: Remedy for Erroneous Overtime Assignment. Closed May 15, 1973.
- Hibbing Taconite Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2075, Grievance Number 3-75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Health and Safety: Disconnecting High Voltage Lines. Closed November 18, 1975.
- Howmet Corporation and United Auto Workers, Local 1243, Case Number 54-30-1461-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Discipline: Discharge for Attempted Theft. Closed June 8, 1976.
- Hoover Ball and Bearing Company and International Association of Machinists, Lodge Number 82, Grievance Number 3-74, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Work Assignment: Maintenance Utility. Closed August 1, 1976.
- Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local Union Number 3, Grievance Number 140, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Recognition: Management's Rights; Removal of Work from Bargaining Unit; Consolidation of Departments and Jobs. Closed February 11, 1975.
- Kelsey-Hayes Company and United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 114, Grievance Number 1-2875, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Sub-contracting: Guarding Sold Property. Closed November 11, 1976.
- The City of Lansing Police Department and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 141, Case Number MERC 376-L, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Grievances and Arbitration; Discipline: Management Rights. Closed January 7, 1976
- Lindell Drop Forge Company and International Union, United Auto Workers Local 724, Grievance Number 2982, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Call-in Pay. Closed May 24, 1976.
- Lundberg Screw Products Company and United Auto Workers Local 724, Grievance Number 263, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed February 12, 1975.
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International Union, Local (AFL-CIO) Case Number 53-30-0156-73, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Closed March 8, 1976.
- Michigan Chemical Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 7-224, Grievance Number 75-19, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Misappropriation of Company Property. Closed June 16, 1975
- Midwest Steel division of National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievance Number III-73-1001, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Work Assignment: Computer Maintenance. Closed February 26, 1975
- Green River Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4959, Grievance Number 3-748-74, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Wages: Incentives Monthly Calculations; Date Shipped. Closed August 29, 1975
- Midwest Steel Division - National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievances III-74-1014, 1015, 1016, 1017, 3003, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Safety and Health: Working Alone in Isolated Areas. Closed May 6, 1975.
- Midwest Steel Division - National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievance III-73-1030, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Temporary Transfers; Special Allowance. Closed May 16, 1975
- Midwest Steel Division - National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievance II-72-1059, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Wages: Incentive Plan; Adequacy of. Closed July 18, 1975
- Midwest Steel Division - National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievance Numbers III-73-1005 and III-73-1014, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Contracting Out: In-Plant Scrap Hauling. Closed June 18, 1975
- Midwest Steel Division - National Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103, Grievance Number II-73-1035, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Seniority: Demolition; Lack of Physical Ability Female Employees. Closed June 24, 1975.
- Milwaukee Forge company and United Steelworkers of America Local 3205, Grievance Number 31, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Discipline: Quitting Early. Closed June 22, 1973.
- Pennwalt Corporation and United steelworkers of America, Grievance Number 367-C, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Overtime: Failure to request relief. Closed January 29, 1974
- Milwaukee Forge Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 3205, Grievance Number 32, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- National Acme Division Acme Cleveland Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 145, Grievance Number F-2389, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Recognition: Performance of Bargaining Unit Work by Supervisors. Closed January 24, 1973
- Noren Pattern and Foundry Company and International Molders and allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 120, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Work Assignments: Overtime. Grievance dated February 27, 1973. Closed December 3, 1973.
- Northwestern Steel and Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 63, Grievances E-224, E-275, and E-277, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Work Assignments: Yard 6 Gantry Crane Maintenance. Closed August 29, 1974.
- Northwestern Steel and Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 63, Grievance E-156, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Scheduling and Overtime: Cancelling Sixth Scheduled Day. Closed August 29, 1974
- A.O. Smith Corporation - Electric Motor Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1977. Grievance 72/75, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Wages: Incentive Plan; Adequacy of Standards. Closed September 20, 1974
- A.O. Smith Corporation Electric Motor Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1977, Grievance Numbers 72/79 and 72/80, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Restricting Production. Closed December 11, 1974.
- A.O. Smith Corporation Electric Motor Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1977, Grievance 72/82, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Seniority: Shift Preference. Closed December 11, 1974.
- Swift and Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America, AFL-CIO, Grievance Number 201, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed February 13, 1973.
- Swift and Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO Grievance Number 191, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Classification: Pipefitter or Plumber. Closed February 13, 1973.
- City of Sterling Heights and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 1557, Grievance Number 27, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Vacation Time. Closed August 18, 1971.
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and Communication Workers of America, Grievance Number 71-30-0089-72, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Seniority: Schedule Assignments; Telephone Repeater men. Closed March 20, 1973.
- Spartans Industries, Incorporated and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 976, Retail Clerks international Association, AFL-CIO, Case 5430 0098 66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Discipline: Changing Price Ticket and Purchasing. Closed July 29, 1966.
- Sealed Power Corporation and United auto Workers Local 637 Grievance Number 7651, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Grievance Procedure: New Grievance on a settled issue. Closed March 29, 1965.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 433-805-1129, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Representation: Preferential Seniority During Temporary Layoffs. Closed January 19, 1961.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 1108, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Discharge for overstaying a leave of absence. Closed January 19, 1961
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, grievance 2439, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Frequent Garnishments. Closed January 29, 1962.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 1626, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Working Hours: Overtime on short notice: Reporting for work after refusing to work. Closed December 3, 1964
- Albion Malleable Iron company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 2756, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Careless Work. Closed December 3, 1964.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 3132, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Insubordination and threatening Supervisor. Closed December 3, 1964.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 3713, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Assault on Supervisors. Closed December 16, 1965
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 2172, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Excessive Garnishments. Closed December 16, 1965.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers, Local 474, Grievance 4777, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Absenteeism. Closed September 26, 1966
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 4604, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Wages: Call-in Pay for Saturday. Closed September 26, 1966
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 4195, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Procedural Arbitration. Closed December 23, 1966
- Hayes-Albion Corporation and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 9788, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Representation: Pay for Full Time Union Representative. Closed November 23, 1971.
- Hayes-Albion Corporation and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 0002 and 0141, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Representation: Full Time representatives; Alternates. Closed November 23, 1971.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 1132, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Overtime Schedules: Method of "informing" the Steward. Closed January 19, 1961.
- Albion Malleable Iron Company and United Auto Workers Local 474, Grievance 1128, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Representation: Overtime for Stewards of Departments on Staggered Shifts. Closed January 19, 1961
- Allied Paper Company and United Paperworkers, Case 54-30-0387-75, Grievances 74, 76, 77 and 84, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Working Hours: Equalization of Overtime. Closed January 12, 1976
- Carpenter Technology Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2215, Grievance ME-269, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Wages: Premium Pay; Change in work schedule. Closed April 15, 1970.
- Carpenter Technology Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2215, Grievance GG-267, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Incentives: Adjustment of changed conditions. Closed April 15, 1970.
- Carpenter Technology Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2215, Grievance ME-168, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Discontinuance of Facilities; Bumping to Retain Employment. Closed April 15, 1970.
- Carpenter Technology Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2215, Grievance CM-367, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Seniority: Reduction in Force; Ability and Seniority. Closed June 11, 1970.
- Carpenter Technology Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2215, Grievance CM-168, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Seniority: Ability Gratuitous Trial Period. Closed April 15, 1970.
- City of Detroit Department of P and R and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees District 77, Grievance 364, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Seniority: Layoffs; Contracting Out. Closed April 25, 1973
- City of Detroit Civic Center Commission District 77 and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Grievance 703, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed February 11, 1974.
- City of Detroit Board of Assessors and Senior Accountants and Analysts Association, Grievance Assessors 001, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Working conditions: Existing Benefits; Use of City-Owned Vehicles. Closed June 12, 1974.
- City of Pontiac-Point and Fire Fighters Union Local 376, Grievance 106, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Fringe Benefits: Sick Leave; Value of Unused Leave Days. Closed April 6, 1971.
- Simpson Manufacturing Company and Litchfield independent Workers Union, Grievance 00215, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Arbitrability: Timeliness of Grievance; Continuing Violations. Closed December 3, 1975.
- Pan American World Railways and United Plant Guard Workers of America (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Settled at Hearing. No date.
- City of Pontiac, Pontiac Municipal Employees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Discharge of Gary Allison - Discipline: Insubordination. Closed November 28, 1973.
- Prudential Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Settled before hearing. No date.
- Reactive Metals, Incorporated, and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-509, Grievance 20-M-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Overtime Distribution. Closed June 30, 1971
- Reactive Metals, Incorporated and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union Local 2155, Grievance Number 69-15, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Discipline: Sleeping on Company Property. Closed October 27, 1970.
- Reactive Metals, Incorporated and United Steelworkers of America Local 2155, Grievance Number 67-10, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Wages: Classification; Spectrograph and Quant meter Operator. Closed May 16, 1968.
- Remington-Rand and International Union of Electrical Workers Business Machines Local 459, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  John Charland Grievance - Discharge: "Just Cause." Closed June 2, 1971
- Ford Motor Company (Chicago Plant?) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 225, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Recognition: Work Assignment; Work of Protective Nature. Closed November 5, 1965.
- Ford Motor Company and Pattern Makers Association, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Seniority: Layoffs; Apprentices and Journeymen. Closed August 4, 1960.
- Ford Motor Company (Livonia Plant) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 114, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Management's Rights; Contracting Out. Fire Protection Inspection. Closed March 29, 1963
- Ford Motor Company (Wixom Plant) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 114, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Work Assignments; Local Agreement, "Additional Work Load Burden." Closed July 26, 1963.
- Ford Motor Company (Glass Division - Nashville) and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Shift Preference. Closed September 6, 1963.
- Ford Motor Company (Dearborn, Michigan) and Pattern Makers League, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Recognition: Work Assignment; Run off on Hammer Forms. Closed April 6, 1962.
- Ford Motor Company (Sheffield, Alabama) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 601, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Shift Preference: Contracts; National and Local Bargaining. Closed May 7, 1969
- Ford Motor Company and Pattern Makers of Detroit and Vicinity, Grievance Numbers 8, 10, 12, 13, and 15-1967, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Closed June 2, 1969
- General Motors Corporation and Pattern Makers League of North America, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Strikes, Lockouts. Closed June 20, 1962
- Great Lakes Steel and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Discipline: Assaulting Supervisor. Closed April 1, 1970
- Gerber Products Company and Local 530, Retail, wholesale, etcetera, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Absence: Deer Hunting. Closed July 22, 1963.
- General Cable Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6222, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Job Evaluation: Braider (Wire) Operator. Closed March 30, 1971
- General Cable Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 6222, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Incentive: Standard; Cord Coiling Operation. Closed May 19, 1971
- Grand Machine Company and International Union of electrical Workers, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Seniority: Loss of; Absence without notice. Closed May 20, 1966
- Grand Rapids Metalcraft and United Auto Workers Local 19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed March 10, 1970
- Grand Rapids Metalcraft and United Auto Workers Local 19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Fringe Benefits: Discrimination, Insurance Premiums During Pregnancy Leave. Closed March 10, 1970.
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Classification: Balling Drum Operator. Closed December 6, 1967
- Saint Regis Paper Company and Printing Specialties Local 705, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Seniority: Promotions; Relative Ability. Closed July 6, 1977
- Sealed Power Corporation and United Auto Workers (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Pension Fund. No date.
- Sears, Roebuck and Company and Teamsters Local 243, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Discharge. Closed June 7, 1978
- Stroh Brewery Company and International Association of Machinists, etcetera, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Absence; Union Business. Closed March 29, 1976
- Sparrow Hospital and Building Service Employees Union Local 29 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Governor's Special Commission. No date.
- Southwestern Bell and Communication Workers of America, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Seniority: demotion for incompetence. Closed May 17, 1976.
- Standard Oil Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Seniority: Layoffs; Permanent Reduction in Force. Closed January 26, 1965.
- Teledyne Wisconsin Motors and United Auto Workers, Grievance D-998, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Sub-contracting. Closed May 18, 1976.
- Teledyne Wisconsin Motors and United Auto Workers, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Wages: Classification; Cutter Grinders/Toolmakers. Closed May 18, 1976.
- City of Warren and Warren Professional Firefighters Union., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Wages: Cost of Living Allowance. Closed January 21, 1975
- Bostrom - Universal Oil Products and Independent Union of Bostrum Employees, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Distribution of Overtime. Closed October 15, 1974.
- Bostrom - Universal Oil Products and Independent Union of Bostrum Employees, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Wages: Incentives, Red Circle Rate. Closed October 15, 1974.
- Bostrom - Universal Oil Products and Independent Union of Bostrum Employees, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Withdrawal of Appeals; Without Prejudice. Closed October 11, 1974.
- Washburn Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Discipline: Refusal to Work Overtime. Closed May 4, 1973.
- Washburn Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 5705, Grievance 73-17, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Refusal to Work Overtime. Closed December 20, 1974.
- Washburn Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 5705, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Work Assignments: Crew Size; Number 1 Rod Mill. Closed December 20, 1974
- Boaz Siegel, Claimant, and Wayne State University, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Payment of unused vacation days. Closed November 1, 1974
- Wayne State University and Professional and Administrative Association, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Forced vacations during notice of layoff period. Closed September 9, 1975
- WKMF, Incorporated, and National Association Broadcast Employees and Technicians (AFL-CIO) Local 46, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Falsifications of Program Log Entries. Closed December 17, 1973.
- Whitehead and Kales Company and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 114, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  James Doig Grievance - Discipline: Working while under the influence of alcohol. Closed January 19, 1976.
- Whitehead and Kales Company and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 114, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Discharge: Discipline; Multiple Offences. Closed April 19, 1976
- West Bloomfield Board of Education and West Bloomfield Education Association, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Teacher Evaluations: Form and Content Reports. Closed November 24, 1975
- Titanium Metals Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Absenteeism. Closed December 30, 1964.
- Trans World Airlines, Incorporated and Air Lines Dispatcher's Association, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Recognition: Bargaining; Reopening Furlough Pay clause. Closed November 1, 1963.
- Unit Rail Anchor Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Closed December 31, 1968
- Titanium Metals Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Salary: Time of Payment; Application of Agreement Terms. Closed July 2, 1968.
- True Temper Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Wages: Job Evaluation. Closed February 10, 1971
- United States Steel Supply (United States Steel Corporation), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Scheduling: Normal Work Day. Closed February 10, 1962
- Vernors Incorporated and Retail and Wholesale Distributors Union Local 297, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Discipline: Fighting. Closed February 10, 1971.
- Vernors Incorporated and Retail and Wholesale Distributors Union Local 297, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Discipline: Theft of Company Property. Closed May 25, 1971
- Vickers Incorporated (Sperry Rand Corporation), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Recognition: Assignment of Mail Car Driving to Excluded Employees. Closed January 10, 1969
- Vulcan Mold and Iron Company, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Work Assignments: Temporary Transfers; Job Description. Closed October 14, 1964.
- Vulcan Mold and Iron Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Seniority: Ability: Bumping in a Force Reduction. Closed May 21, 1964.